nbk.com 2013-11-27

# Privacy | NBK Group Website

### 

Our strategically placed offices across the world, gives us extensive global reach. 

View Map

  * Home
  * Privacy

**NBK.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. We shall never sell your personal information to other companies for their independent marketing purposes. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to prevent unauthorized access to your personal information and to protect you against the criminal misuse of that information. We restrict access to your account(s) to only those employees involved in providing the services you've requested.

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the NBK.com website.

 **IP Address and Cookies**

Your IP address may be used to gather broad demographic information. In order to provide better service, we may use "cookies". Our site may use cookies for administrative purposes and to enhance your online experience by keeping track of your behavior within the site and to make sure you do not see the same special offers repeatedly.

Your contact information may be used by NBK to contact the you when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the Choice section below.

 **Links to Third Party Sites**

This site contains links to other sites. Third party web sites have different privacy policies and/or security standards governing their sites, we advise you to review the privacy policies and terms and conditions of these sites prior to providing any personal information. Links to non-NBK web sites are provided solely for information purposes. If you choose to access such sites NBK.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.

 **Security**

While we have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control and while we have appropriate firewalls in place to block unauthorized access to any user data stored on our servers, we shall not be responsible for any loss, misuse, alternation, or unauthorized access to any such information or data.

 **Children's Guidelines**

This site is not intended to be used by children.

 **Choice**

When we request information about you, you are given the choice not to receive communications from our partners. You may remove your information from our database; choose not to receive future communications, or terminate any of our services.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this site, please contact webmaster@nbk.com

 **Special Offers and Promotions**

Transactions and dealings you enter into with any merchant in respect of any of the special offers and promotions offered on NBK.com shall be effective only between you and the merchant, and NBK shall neither be a party thereto nor be responsible for any such transaction.. National Bank of Kuwait hereby disclaims any warranty, express or implied, connected with any of the content displayed on nbk.com or the information provided by the merchants and/or third parties.

 **National Bank of Kuwait**

NBK.com welcomes your feedback and comments in order to provide its customers with better service.

For any questions or information related to NBK.com third party products, please contact the responsible merchant who holds full responsibility.
